[Music]
starting with this release you can use
warehouse putaway for production output
means you can use the same warehouse
processes as in other
receipts uh it is especially important
for locations where directed putaway and
Peck is enabled because they don't have
any putaway logic for other locations it
also possible to use Warehouse putaway
to align with other areas of application
let's see the demo in a location car
page you can select the warehouse
putaway option in the production output
Warehouse handling field for the
locations with directed putaway and pick
only two options are available no
Warehouse handling and warehouse putaway
for other locations you can also use
inventory
putaway let's investigate the impact of
that setting you can see the release
production order for the manufacturing
of six coffeee makers in the production
Journal start by posting two units
repeat this action to post the remaining
quantity of four units consequently all
six units will have been
posted navigate to The Warehouse
activity lines where you can see two put
away documents generated automatically
during posting that behavior is
controlled by the used putaway worksheet
toggle in the location car page let's
open the first putaway and perform
partial
register then we delete
it and we also open the second one where
you can see quantity
for and delete it as
well navigate to the putaway worksheet
from which we can also create putaway
for production order let's do it for
partial quantity
return to the production order and
change its status to
finished navigate to the finished
production order from which the creation
of Warehouse put away for the remaining
quantity can be triggered this action is
also available in the release production
order next navigate to the warehouse
putaway where the one created from the
putaway worksheet and the one created
for the remaining quantity from the
finished production order be seen we can
also review already registered
putaway what about picking in this
release you can pick more raw materials
than originally requested for production
order for example wherehouse team
decided to send the whole box instead of
uh picking the exact
quantity uh then you can decide what to
do with extra stpl maybe you return it
back to ourhouse or maybe you can use it
for next production order for the later
there is a new flashing method which can
be very useful let's see the demo the
release production order for the
manufacturing of four coffee makers is
available in the components page raw
materials have different flushing
methods a new value pick plus manual
replaces the old manual method the
manual flushing method remains but it
now behaves differently and does not
require picking anymore this change is
consistent with existing backward and
forward flushing methods and provides
additional flexibility to enable manual
to operate in this manner activate the
capability in feature management
additionally a new field allow Warehouse
over pick is visible in the item card
create Warehouse pick and open it notice
that coffee filter basket with manual
flushing method is not there as it
should already be on the open shop floor
we will send full box es of switches and
adjustable feet to production we cannot
do that for the housing as allow
Warehouse overp pick is off for this
item register pick and open production
Journal you'll see the item with manual
flushing method ready to be posted as
well as the adjust aable foot and
housing we don't see switch as it will
be flushed automatically via routing
link code now let's try to change
quantity you can increase the quantity
of coffee filter baskets since there are
plenty in the open shop floor bin and
you control consumption you cannot
adjust the quantity for housing as it
was picked
exactly you can change the quantity for
the adjustable foot because we picked
more than needed
what to do with the switch on off that
uses the pick plus backwards flushing
method add a line manually in the
consumption journal and specify the bin
code or add a new component line with a
manual flushing method ensure the
correct bin code is used
the line will then appear in the
production
Journal if you want to return overp
picked item to Warehouse navigate to the
movement worksheet page and choose the
return overp pick quantity action
thank you for watching you can find more
details about these capabilities in the
release notes also remember to watch
other videos about enhancements about
manufacturing you can find links in the
description